<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Malazan Book of the Fallen on Atharva Shah</title>
    <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/tags/malazan-book-of-the-fallen/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Malazan Book of the Fallen on Atharva Shah</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 00:19:34 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://atharvashah.netlify.app/tags/malazan-book-of-the-fallen/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Deadhouse Gates by Steven Erikson</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/malazan/02-dg-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 00:19:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/malazan/02-dg-review/</guid>
      <description>Rating: 4/5 ⭐
After reading two books in the Malazan Book of the Fallen series, my impression of the writer&amp;rsquo;s work has shifted slightly. While this book, Deadhouse Gates, connected with me on a character-driven level, its bleakness, plethora of new faces, and the desert setting made it slightly more confusing than the previous book, Gardens of the Moon.
Erikson, known for his world-building skills, takes the already extensive cast of characters and places and expands them even further, leaving little respite for readers who struggled to keep up with the first book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Gardens of the Moon by Steven Erikson</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/malazan/01-gotm-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 00:19:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/malazan/01-gotm-review/</guid>
      <description>Rating: 4/5 ⭐
The Gardens of the Moon, the first volume of the Malazan Book of the Fallen, is a sprawling epic fantasy of monumental proportions. The vast array of characters is not just diverse, but uniquely and exquisitely crafted, and each of their roles is pivotal to the story&amp;rsquo;s advancement. There are no throwaway scenes or chapters; every dialogue and action ripples and reverberates throughout the intricate narrative, creating a vivid tapestry of political intrigue, mystical manipulation, and fantastical landscapes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Prelude to my Malazan Book of the Fallen Reading Challenge</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/malazan/prelude-to-malazan-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/malazan/prelude-to-malazan-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Embarking on a massive high fantasy book series is no small feat, especially when you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a breathtaking, complex, and engaging story that spans decades and continents. As an experienced reader of ASoIaF, WoT, Tchaikovsky&amp;rsquo;s works, Mistborn, and the First Law Trilogy, I knew I needed a challenge that would test my mettle.
Enter the Malazan Book of the Fallen. With rave reviews and a reputation for being one of the most epic fantasy series ever written, it seemed like the perfect choice for me.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
