<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>movie review on Atharva Shah</title>
    <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/tags/movie-review/</link>
    <description>Recent content in movie review on Atharva Shah</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 00:18:34 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://atharvashah.netlify.app/tags/movie-review/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>May 2023 Movies: Blockbuster Bonanza</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/movie-review/may-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 00:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/movie-review/may-2023/</guid>
      <description>Amidst the whirlwind of academic and professional commitments, I managed to carve out precious moments to immerse myself in the magic of cinema. The month of May brought forth an array of highly anticipated films, and while my movie-watching endeavors were limited, the experiences I had were truly captivating. This is partly to blame on TV shows like Better Call Saul which I recently finished and Succession which I just picked up and have been obsessively binge watching.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Critical Analysis of Pulp Fiction</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/critical-analysis-pulp-fiction/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 19:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/critical-analysis-pulp-fiction/</guid>
      <description>Narrative Screenplay Costumes and Set Design Soundtrack Camera and Lighting Awards and Accolades Closing Thoughts Directed By : Quentin Tarantino
Release Year : 1994
Starring : John Travolta, Samuel L. Jackson, Uma Thurman, Bruce Willis
Narrative Pulp Fiction adopts a non-linear narrative with three protagonists, namely, Vincent Vega (a quirky hitman), Jules Winnfield (Vega’s partner in crime) and Butch Coolidge(a prizefighter). The movie is split into seven episodic events which do not follow a chronological order.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April 2023 Movies: Spring Screenings</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/movie-review/april-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 00:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/movie-review/april-2023/</guid>
      <description>April 2023 was an exciting month for movie enthusiasts, with a variety of genres and eras represented in the films released and viewed. As an avid movie-goer, I had the opportunity to watch a diverse selection of films, ranging from classic dramas to modern blockbusters. In this monthly post, I&amp;rsquo;ll be sharing my thoughts and opinions on the movies I watched during April 2023. From high-octane action flicks to introspective character studies, these films have something for everyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>March 2023 Movies: Magic and Melodrama</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/movie-review/march-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 00:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/movie-review/march-2023/</guid>
      <description>Lights, camera, action! March 2023 was a month filled with movie magic, and I had the pleasure of watching some truly amazing films. From thought-provoking dramas to side-splitting comedies, this month had it all. I&amp;rsquo;m excited to share my thoughts on the movies I watched, which include the morally challenging First Reformed, the hilarious Game Night, the emotionally charged Spencer, and the classic Edward Scissorhands. I also delved into some cult classics, such as the offbeat Buffalo &amp;lsquo;66 and the spooky Creepshow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>February 2023 Movies: Love and the Big Screen</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/movie-review/february-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/movie-review/february-2023/</guid>
      <description>February was a month for the ages as I indulged in a smorgasbord of movies. From the laugh-out-loud comedy of &amp;ldquo;Rush Hour&amp;rdquo; to the mind-bending sci-fi of &amp;ldquo;Solaris&amp;rdquo; and everything in between, I&amp;rsquo;ve got a lot to say about the films I watched. There were some classics from the past like &amp;ldquo;Nausicaä of the Valley of the Wind&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Porco Rosso,&amp;rdquo; as well as newer releases like &amp;ldquo;Infinity Pool&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Babylon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January 2023 Movies: Toppling My Winter Watchlist</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/movie-review/january-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 00:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/movie-review/january-2023/</guid>
      <description>January 2023 brought a plethora of cinematic experiences my way, and I&amp;rsquo;m eager to share my take on them. From classic films to new releases, my viewing journey was diverse and exciting. This month I tackled a few movies that have been on my watchlist for a while, and I&amp;rsquo;m glad I finally got around to watching them. I enjoyed &amp;ldquo;The Menu&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Moonrise Kingdom,&amp;rdquo; but I was disappointed by &amp;ldquo;To Die For.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
