<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>📚All Posts on Atharva Shah</title>
    <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 📚All Posts on Atharva Shah</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 00:18:34 +0531</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://atharvashah.netlify.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Album Review: Foghorn in the Dawn by 오미일곱 [Omilgop]</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/music-review/foghorn-in-dawn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 00:18:34 +0531</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/music-review/foghorn-in-dawn/</guid>
      <description>Prepare to embark on an ethereal journey through the cosmos as 오미일곱 [Omilgop] unveils their mesmerizing opus, &amp;ldquo;Foghorn in the Dawn.&amp;rdquo; From the very first glance at the album cover, one is immediately ensnared by the aesthetic prowess it exudes, with its resplendent purple hues painting a skyscape that tantalizes the senses. And oh, dear listener, fear not, for the music within matches the allure of this visual masterpiece. It beckons you into a realm of serenity, calmness, and nostalgic introspection, reminiscent of the galaxies themselves tenderly embracing your very being.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Album Review: Demon Days by Gorillaz</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/music-review/demon-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 00:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/music-review/demon-days/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to be reviewing the album &amp;ldquo;Demon Days&amp;rdquo; by Gorillaz, a group that has really put themselves on the map with their unique blend of various genres. This album is truly a soul food and a trip down memory lane. Let&amp;rsquo;s dig in, shall we?
Starting with the hits that have become internet classics, we have the pulsating &amp;ldquo;Feel Good Inc.&amp;rdquo; that has become a fan-favorite and an anthem for the virtual generation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Album Review: Loveless by My Bloody Valentine</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/music-review/loveless-mbv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 00:18:34 +0531</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/music-review/loveless-mbv/</guid>
      <description>As a connoisseur of the avant-garde music scene, I was thrilled to dive headfirst into My Bloody Valentine&amp;rsquo;s iconic album, &amp;ldquo;Loveless.&amp;rdquo; And let me tell you, this album is a wild ride, bursting with the iconic and distinguishing shoegazy sound that enraptured me from my very first listen.
It&amp;rsquo;s no secret that &amp;ldquo;Loveless&amp;rdquo; is a masterclass in shoegaze music, with its harsh and distorted rhythms and tunes that feel so close to you, you&amp;rsquo;ll swear you can reach out and touch them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Album Review: Plastic Beach by Gorillaz</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/music-review/plastic-beach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 00:18:34 +0532</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/music-review/plastic-beach/</guid>
      <description>Gorillaz&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Plastic Beach&amp;rdquo; album is a magnificent work of art that takes the listener on a surreal journey through a digital island filled with both beauty and decay. This is a place where the vibrant colors of the natural world blend with the metallic tones of machinery, and the music echoes that duality with its unique fusion of hip-hop, pop, and psychedelic sounds.
As the third studio album from the animated band, &amp;ldquo;Plastic Beach&amp;rdquo; stands out as a bold and ambitious piece of work that has clearly been meticulously crafted with an acute attention to detail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Album Review: Stratosphere by Duster</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/music-review/stratosphere/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 00:18:34 +0533</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/music-review/stratosphere/</guid>
      <description>Stratosphere, the 1998 slowcore classic by Duster, is a sonic force to be reckoned with. From the minimalist album cover to the dreamy soundscapes, this album evokes a sense of tranquility and longing that is both nostalgic and futuristic. The songs are slow and atmospheric, each one feeling like a journey through space and time, with recurring beats and tempo changes that keep things interesting.
The album&amp;rsquo;s structure is unorthodox and unconventional, with songs flowing into each other seamlessly, creating a hypnotic effect that is both meditative and transportive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Product Series Launch!</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/gumroad-dsa-announcement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 01:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/gumroad-dsa-announcement/</guid>
      <description>Boost Your Interview Success with our Exclusive Digital Product Series We are thrilled to announce the launch of our brand new series of digital products on Gumroad, designed to help you excel in your interviews and land your dream job! Our products are carefully crafted to provide you with the necessary tools and resources to master key concepts, enhance your problem-solving skills, and confidently tackle coding interviews.
Introducing the First Set of Resources We are excited to release the first few resources that are now available for purchase at an incredibly affordable rate:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Quotes from Gothic Violence by Mika Ma</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-gothic-violence-by-mike-ma/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 02:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-gothic-violence-by-mike-ma/</guid>
      <description>TEST Another Test Test 3 Test 4 Emerging from the literary depths, following the consuming voyage through &amp;ldquo;Harassment Architecture,&amp;rdquo; I eagerly embarked upon the haunting terrain of &amp;ldquo;Gothic Violence.&amp;rdquo; In this eagerly awaited sequel, my anticipation was richly rewarded, for within its pages lie potent and evocative fragments of prose that reverberate with profound resonance. While the quantity may be lesser than its predecessor, the impact remains undiminished, as the narrative unfurls with a potent force, relentlessly piercing the reader&amp;rsquo;s consciousness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Quotes from Harassment Architechture by Mika Ma</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-harassment-architechture-by-mike-ma/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 01:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-harassment-architechture-by-mike-ma/</guid>
      <description>Immersed within the profound literary labyrinth that is Mike Ma&amp;rsquo;s oeuvre, I stumbled upon an enigmatic tapestry of words that left me astounded, pondering why this luminary artist had not yet ascended to the pinnacles of recognition. Within the tapestry of his creations, one finds a captivating amalgamation of satire, philosophy, and humor that defies conventional categorization. Yet, it is not through the predictable lens of conventional narratives that Ma&amp;rsquo;s genius shines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 2023 Movies: Blockbuster Bonanza</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/movie-review/may-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 00:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/movie-review/may-2023/</guid>
      <description>Amidst the whirlwind of academic and professional commitments, I managed to carve out precious moments to immerse myself in the magic of cinema. The month of May brought forth an array of highly anticipated films, and while my movie-watching endeavors were limited, the experiences I had were truly captivating. This is partly to blame on TV shows like Better Call Saul which I recently finished and Succession which I just picked up and have been obsessively binge watching.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting Up CI/CD to Netlify for Static Sites via Github</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/netlify-ci-cd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 19:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/netlify-ci-cd/</guid>
      <description>Description I. Introduction II. Setting Up a Netlify Account III. Setting Up CI/CD to Netlify Configuring the Build Settings on Netlify Configuring the Deployment Settings on Netlify IV. Setting Up CI/CD with Github Actions Introduction to Github Actions Creating a Github Actions Workflow for the Static Site Configuring the Workflow to Deploy to Netlify V. Best Practices for CI/CD with Netlify and Github VI. Troubleshooting CI/CD Issues VII. Conclusion Description This article provides step-by-step instructions on how to set up continuous integration and continuous deployment (CI/CD) to Netlify for static site deployments using Github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Critical Analysis of Pulp Fiction</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/critical-analysis-pulp-fiction/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 19:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/critical-analysis-pulp-fiction/</guid>
      <description>Narrative Screenplay Costumes and Set Design Soundtrack Camera and Lighting Awards and Accolades Closing Thoughts Directed By : Quentin Tarantino
Release Year : 1994
Starring : John Travolta, Samuel L. Jackson, Uma Thurman, Bruce Willis
Narrative Pulp Fiction adopts a non-linear narrative with three protagonists, namely, Vincent Vega (a quirky hitman), Jules Winnfield (Vega’s partner in crime) and Butch Coolidge(a prizefighter). The movie is split into seven episodic events which do not follow a chronological order.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Django Crypto App Part 3: Wrap-Up and Testing</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/django-crypto-app/part3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 23:20:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/django-crypto-app/part3/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Test Driven Development Approach Explained URL Testing Model Testing View Testing Writing Tests Testing URLS Testing Models Testing Views How to Run Tests Conclusion Introduction Welcome to the final part of the 3-part technical tutorial series, where have been building a Django project that enables users to manage their cryptocurrency portfolios. To implement the functionalities and additional features, we&amp;rsquo;ll be utilizing API calls to coingecko or any other cryptocurrency API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Django Crypto App Part 2: Templates, Views and URLs</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/django-crypto-app/part2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 23:19:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/django-crypto-app/part2/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Setting up the URLs Setting Up Templates Setting Up Views Signup Login Screen Forgot Password Page Password Reset Email Password Reset Success Home Page Add Currency / Search Result Page Wallet Page Run the crypto app Conclusion Introduction Welcome to the second part of the 3-part technical tutorial series, where we&amp;rsquo;ll be building a Django project that enables users to manage their cryptocurrency portfolios. To implement the functionalities and additional features, we&amp;rsquo;ll be utilizing API calls to coingecko or any other cryptocurrency API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Django Crypto App Part 1: Functional Requirements and Setup</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/django-crypto-app/part1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 23:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/django-crypto-app/part1/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents Table of contents Introduction Defining Functional Requirements Tech Stack Planned Endpoints Creating a New Django Project Configuring settings.py Configuring urls.py Create App Models Registering Models in Admin Conclusion Introduction Welcome to this 3-part technical tutorial series, where we&amp;rsquo;ll be building a Django project that enables users to manage their cryptocurrency portfolios. To implement the functionalities and additional features, we&amp;rsquo;ll be utilizing API calls to coingecko or any other cryptocurrency API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Deadhouse Gates by Steven Erikson</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/malazan/02-dg-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 00:19:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/malazan/02-dg-review/</guid>
      <description>Rating: 4/5 ⭐
After reading two books in the Malazan Book of the Fallen series, my impression of the writer&amp;rsquo;s work has shifted slightly. While this book, Deadhouse Gates, connected with me on a character-driven level, its bleakness, plethora of new faces, and the desert setting made it slightly more confusing than the previous book, Gardens of the Moon.
Erikson, known for his world-building skills, takes the already extensive cast of characters and places and expands them even further, leaving little respite for readers who struggled to keep up with the first book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Gardens of the Moon by Steven Erikson</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/malazan/01-gotm-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 00:19:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/malazan/01-gotm-review/</guid>
      <description>Rating: 4/5 ⭐
The Gardens of the Moon, the first volume of the Malazan Book of the Fallen, is a sprawling epic fantasy of monumental proportions. The vast array of characters is not just diverse, but uniquely and exquisitely crafted, and each of their roles is pivotal to the story&amp;rsquo;s advancement. There are no throwaway scenes or chapters; every dialogue and action ripples and reverberates throughout the intricate narrative, creating a vivid tapestry of political intrigue, mystical manipulation, and fantastical landscapes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April 2023 Movies: Spring Screenings</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/movie-review/april-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 00:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/movie-review/april-2023/</guid>
      <description>April 2023 was an exciting month for movie enthusiasts, with a variety of genres and eras represented in the films released and viewed. As an avid movie-goer, I had the opportunity to watch a diverse selection of films, ranging from classic dramas to modern blockbusters. In this monthly post, I&amp;rsquo;ll be sharing my thoughts and opinions on the movies I watched during April 2023. From high-octane action flicks to introspective character studies, these films have something for everyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Quotes from H.P. Lovecraft</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-h.p.-lovecraft/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 23:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-h.p.-lovecraft/</guid>
      <description>A chieftain of the macabre and the weird, H.P. Lovecraft is one of the most influential horror writers of the 20th century. His stories are filled with the supernatural and the occult and his works have inspired many other writers, including Stephen King, Neil Gaiman, and Clive Barker. Here are some of the best quotes from H.P. Lovecraft. My very personal favorites.
There are not many persons who know what wonders are opened to them in the stories and visions of their youth; for when as children we learn and dream, we think but half-formed thoughts, and when as men we try to remember, we are dulled and prosaic with the poison of life</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>March 2023 Movies: Magic and Melodrama</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/movie-review/march-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 00:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/movie-review/march-2023/</guid>
      <description>Lights, camera, action! March 2023 was a month filled with movie magic, and I had the pleasure of watching some truly amazing films. From thought-provoking dramas to side-splitting comedies, this month had it all. I&amp;rsquo;m excited to share my thoughts on the movies I watched, which include the morally challenging First Reformed, the hilarious Game Night, the emotionally charged Spencer, and the classic Edward Scissorhands. I also delved into some cult classics, such as the offbeat Buffalo &amp;lsquo;66 and the spooky Creepshow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Awesome Youtube Channels I am Subscribed To</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/lists/list-favorite-youtube-channels/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 01:18:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/lists/list-favorite-youtube-channels/</guid>
      <description>Technology Comedy Skits Interviews and Banter Gaming Music Movies and TV Misc Herein lies a compilation of my most cherished YouTube channels. Having subscribed to most of these for a number of years, I make it a point to regularly tune into their content. These channels are categorized for your ease of reference, and will be continually updated as I stumble upon more gems. I invite you to share your own recommendations in the comments section below, as this list shall remain perpetual.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Awesome Podcasts I am Listening To</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/lists/list-favorite-podcasts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 01:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/lists/list-favorite-podcasts/</guid>
      <description>Allow me to present a compendium of the podcasts to which I have been attending for some duration. Through my consistent engagement with this medium, I have unearthed a trove of noteworthy podcasts. It is my intention to continue expanding this list as I encounter additional stimulating programs. Please note that this registry is not arranged in any specific sequence, and I must emphasize that it is primarily a personal memorandum rather than an article for public dissemination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Prelude to my Malazan Book of the Fallen Reading Challenge</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/malazan/prelude-to-malazan-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/malazan/prelude-to-malazan-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Embarking on a massive high fantasy book series is no small feat, especially when you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a breathtaking, complex, and engaging story that spans decades and continents. As an experienced reader of ASoIaF, WoT, Tchaikovsky&amp;rsquo;s works, Mistborn, and the First Law Trilogy, I knew I needed a challenge that would test my mettle.
Enter the Malazan Book of the Fallen. With rave reviews and a reputation for being one of the most epic fantasy series ever written, it seemed like the perfect choice for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>February 2023 Movies: Love and the Big Screen</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/movie-review/february-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/movie-review/february-2023/</guid>
      <description>February was a month for the ages as I indulged in a smorgasbord of movies. From the laugh-out-loud comedy of &amp;ldquo;Rush Hour&amp;rdquo; to the mind-bending sci-fi of &amp;ldquo;Solaris&amp;rdquo; and everything in between, I&amp;rsquo;ve got a lot to say about the films I watched. There were some classics from the past like &amp;ldquo;Nausicaä of the Valley of the Wind&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Porco Rosso,&amp;rdquo; as well as newer releases like &amp;ldquo;Infinity Pool&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Babylon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Django ORM Cheatsheet &#43; Exercises</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/django-orm-exercises/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 01:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/django-orm-exercises/</guid>
      <description>Querying Django Models with Examples Terminology Models Used in the Examples QuerySet API Exercises Query 1: Fetching all books from the database Query 2: Fetching selected columns from the Books table Query 3: Filtering records based on a condition Query 4: Filtering records based on multiple conditions Query 5: Searching records based on a substring Query 6: Retrieve authors with specific primary keys Query 7: Retrieve authors who joined after a specific date Query 8: Retrieve distinct publisher last name Query 9: Retrieve the latest joined author and the earliest joined publisher Query 10: Retrieve the first name, last name, and join date of the most recently joined author Query 11: Retrieve Authors Joined After 2013 Query 12: Calculate Total Price of Books Written by Popular Authors Query 13: Retrieve Titles of Books Written by Authors with &amp;lsquo;a&amp;rsquo; in their Firstname Query 14: Calculate Average Book Price of Selected Authors Query 15: Retrieve first name of authors and their recommended author&amp;rsquo;s first name Query 16: Retrieve authors whose books are published by a specific publisher Query 17: Add followers to an author Query 18: Set followers for an author Query 19: Add a follower to an author Query 20: Remove a follower from an author Query 21: Retrieve the first names of all authors followed by the user with primary key (pk) equal to 1 Query 22: Retrieve all authors who have books with titles containing the string &amp;ldquo;tle&amp;rdquo; Query 23: Retrieve all authors whose first name starts with the letter &amp;ldquo;a&amp;rdquo; and either have a popularity score greater than 5 or joined the platform after the year 2014 Query 24: Retrieve the author with primary key (pk) equal to 1 Query 25: Retrieve the first 10 authors in the database Query 26: Retrieve the first and last author in the database with a popularity score of 7 Query 27: Retrieve all authors whose joindate year is greater than or equal to 2012, popularity_score is greater than or equal to 4, joindate day is greater than or equal to 12, and firstname starts with &amp;lsquo;a&amp;rsquo; Query 28: Retrieve all authors whose joindate year is not equal to 2012 Query 29: Retrieve the oldest joindate among all authors, the newest joindate among all authors, the average popularity_score of all authors, and the sum of price of all books Query 30: Retrieve all authors who have not been recommended by anyone Query 31: Retrieve all books that have an author, and all books that have an author who has not been recommended by anyone Query 32: Calculate the sum of the price of all books authored by the author with primary key (pk) equal to 1 Query 33: Retrieve the title of the most recently published book Query 34: Calculate the average price of all books Query 35: Calculate the maximum popularity score of all the publishers that have published a book written by the author with primary key 1 Query 36: Count Authors with Books containing &amp;lsquo;ab&amp;rsquo; in the title Query 37: Filter Authors by Number of Followers Query 38: Average Popularity Score of Authors who joined after 20th Sep 2014 Query 39: Filter Books by Authors who have written more than 10 Books Query 40: Filter Books by Title Count Conclusion Querying Django Models with Examples In Django, querying the database is an essential task when working with models.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use ChatGPT to Generate Project UML Diagrams: A Step-by-Step Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/uml-diagrams-with-chatgpt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 01:19:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/uml-diagrams-with-chatgpt/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you tired of spending hours designing UML diagrams for your projects? Look no further than ChatGPT, a powerful language model that can generate PlantUML code based on your project description. In this tutorial, we will guide you through the steps to use ChatGPT to generate UML diagrams for your projects in just a few clicks.
Step 1: Write Your Project Description The first step is to write your project description or title.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January 2023 Movies: Toppling My Winter Watchlist</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/movie-review/january-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 00:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/movie-review/january-2023/</guid>
      <description>January 2023 brought a plethora of cinematic experiences my way, and I&amp;rsquo;m eager to share my take on them. From classic films to new releases, my viewing journey was diverse and exciting. This month I tackled a few movies that have been on my watchlist for a while, and I&amp;rsquo;m glad I finally got around to watching them. I enjoyed &amp;ldquo;The Menu&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Moonrise Kingdom,&amp;rdquo; but I was disappointed by &amp;ldquo;To Die For.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I am Learning in 2023</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/what-i-am-learning-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 01:19:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/what-i-am-learning-2023/</guid>
      <description>Django 🚀2023 is here, and I&amp;rsquo;m ready to blast off into the world of new tech! First up on my list is the one and only Django 🤘. This bad boy is known for its ease of use and flexibility, plus it&amp;rsquo;s got a huge community of cool kids using it. I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to dive deeper and discover all its hidden gems like the ORM, admin interface, and built-in security features.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating into the Future: An Exploration of Effective Accelerationism and its Impact on AI and Society</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/effective-accelerationism/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 01:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/effective-accelerationism/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Brief overview of accelerationism The advent of AI and its impact on society Theories of Accelerationism Historical context of accelerationism Left and right-wing accelerationism Critiques of accelerationism AI and the Future of Society Advancements in AI technology Potential consequences of widespread AI integration Ethical considerations of AI development Accelerationism and Transhumanism: A Complex Intersection The intersection of accelerationism and transhumanism Potential benefits and drawbacks of merging technology with humanity Final thoughts on the Post-AI Society Introduction Yo, what&amp;rsquo;s good, internet?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating victory at CRIF Hackathon 2023</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/crif-hackathon-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 23:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/crif-hackathon-2023/</guid>
      <description>Winning a hackathon is an incredible feeling, and it&amp;rsquo;s even more special when it&amp;rsquo;s your very first one. The adrenaline rush of competing against some of the brightest minds in the industry, the satisfaction of solving complex problems, and the thrill of being recognized for your hard work are all emotions that are hard to put into words. In this article, I&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through the journey of our team who recently won their first ever hackathon, the CRIF Hackathon 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Quotes from First Law Trilogy by Joe Abercrombie</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-first-law-trilogy-by-joe-abercrombie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 23:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-first-law-trilogy-by-joe-abercrombie/</guid>
      <description>The Blade Itself Once you&amp;rsquo;ve got a task to do, it&amp;rsquo;s better to do it than live with the fear of it. The more you learn, the more you realize how little you know. Still, the struggle itself is worthwhile. Knowledge is the root of power, after all. You have to learn to love the small things in life, like a hot bath. You have to love the small things, when you have nothing else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Quotes from Nevernight Trilogy by Jay Kristoff</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-nevernight-trilogy-by-jay-kristoff/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 23:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-nevernight-trilogy-by-jay-kristoff/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s not mess around here. This series has just more than quotes to offer so I have included rich descriptive texts that boil the blood and wake something deep inside. Here&amp;rsquo;s to the good times fellas. Read on for some savage blood-curdling brutalism.
The deed is done. The war is won. And at the last, gentlefriend, her song is sung. I suppose you can say you know her now, at least as well as I did.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Quotes from Realm of the Elderlings by Robin Hobb</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-realm-of-the-elderlings-by-robin-hobb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 23:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-realm-of-the-elderlings-by-robin-hobb/</guid>
      <description>Currently, I have only managed to finish off the first trilogy in the mammoth that Realm of the Elderlings happens to be but I plan to power through the series soon and add the remainder of the quotes so sit back and enjoy what I have to offer. If you feel a few hidden gems are missing, email me!
Farseer Trilogy Assassin’s Apprentice When you cut pieces out of the truth to avoid looking like a fool you end up looking like a moron instead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Quotes from Sandman (Graphic Novel) by Neil Gaiman</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-sandman-graphic-novel-by-neil-gaiman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 23:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-sandman-graphic-novel-by-neil-gaiman/</guid>
      <description>Vol 1: Preludes and Nocturnes But where shall wisdom be found? And where is the place of understanding? Man knoweth not the price thereof; neither is it found in the land of the living … for the price of wisdom is above rubies. CHORONZON: I am a dire wolf, prey-stalking, lethal prowler. MORPHEUS: I am a hunter, horse-mounted, wolf-stabbing. CHORONZON: I am a horsefly, horse-stinging, hunter-throwing. MORPHEUS: I am a spider, fly-consuming, eight legged.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Quotes from The Witcher Series by Andrzej Sapkowski</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-witcher-series-by-andrzej-sapkowski/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 23:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-witcher-series-by-andrzej-sapkowski/</guid>
      <description>The Last Wish You make as good a fisherman as a goat’s arse makes a trumpet. &amp;ldquo;Kings,” continued Calanthe, “divide people into two categories—those they order around, and those they buy—because they adhere to the old and banal truth that everyone can be bought. &amp;ldquo;The sun shines differently, the air is different, water is not as it used to be. The things we used to eat, made use of, are dying, diminishing, deteriorating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Quotes from Watchmen (Graphic Novel) by Alan Moore</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-watchmen-graphic-novel-by-alan-moore/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 23:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-watchmen-graphic-novel-by-alan-moore/</guid>
      <description>Heard joke once: Man goes to doctor. Says he&amp;rsquo;s depressed. Says life seems harsh and cruel. Says he feels all alone in a threatening world where what lies ahead is vague and uncertain. Doctor says, &amp;ldquo;Treatment is simple. Great clown Pagliacci is in town tonight. Go and see him. That should pick you up.&amp;rdquo; Man bursts into tears. Says, &amp;ldquo;But doctor&amp;hellip;I am Pagliacci. Looked at sky through smoke heavy with human fat and God was not there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Quotes from Book of the Ancestors Trilogy by Mark Lawrence</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-book-of-the-ancestors-trilogy-by-mark-lawrence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 23:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-book-of-the-ancestors-trilogy-by-mark-lawrence/</guid>
      <description>A book is as dangerous as any journey you might take. The person who closes the back cover may not be the same one that opened the front one. Treat them with respect. Your death has not been waiting for your arrival at the appointed hour: it has, for all the years of your life, been racing towards you with the fierce velocity of time&amp;rsquo;s arrow. It cannot be evaded, it cannot be bargained with, deflected or placated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Quotes from Broken Empire Trilogy by Mark Lawrence</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-broken-empire-trilogy-by-mark-lawrence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 23:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/personal/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-broken-empire-trilogy-by-mark-lawrence/</guid>
      <description>Prince of Thorns Memories are dangerous things. You turn them over and over, until you know every touch and corner, but still you&amp;rsquo;ll find an edge to cut you. Each day the memories weigh a little heavier. Each day they drag you down that bit further. You wind them around you, a single thread at a time, and you weave your own shroud, you build a cocoon, and in it madness grows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/about/</guid>
      <description>Get to know me better</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
