<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>lists on Atharva Shah</title>
    <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/tags/lists/</link>
    <description>Recent content in lists on Atharva Shah</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 01:18:35 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://atharvashah.netlify.app/tags/lists/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Awesome Youtube Channels I am Subscribed To</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/personal/lists/list-favorite-youtube-channels/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 01:18:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/personal/lists/list-favorite-youtube-channels/</guid>
      <description>Technology Comedy Skits Interviews and Banter Gaming Music Movies and TV Misc Herein lies a compilation of my most cherished YouTube channels. Having subscribed to most of these for a number of years, I make it a point to regularly tune into their content. These channels are categorized for your ease of reference, and will be continually updated as I stumble upon more gems. I invite you to share your own recommendations in the comments section below, as this list shall remain perpetual.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Awesome Podcasts I am Listening To</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/personal/lists/list-favorite-podcasts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 01:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/personal/lists/list-favorite-podcasts/</guid>
      <description>Allow me to present a compendium of the podcasts to which I have been attending for some duration. Through my consistent engagement with this medium, I have unearthed a trove of noteworthy podcasts. It is my intention to continue expanding this list as I encounter additional stimulating programs. Please note that this registry is not arranged in any specific sequence, and I must emphasize that it is primarily a personal memorandum rather than an article for public dissemination.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
