<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Atharva Shah</title>
    <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Atharva Shah</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 23:18:34 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Best Quotes from First Law Trilogy by Joe Abercrombie</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-first-law-trilogy-by-joe-abercrombie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 23:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-first-law-trilogy-by-joe-abercrombie/</guid>
      <description>The Blade Itself Once you&amp;rsquo;ve got a task to do, it&amp;rsquo;s better to do it than live with the fear of it. The more you learn, the more you realize how little you know. Still, the struggle itself is worthwhile. Knowledge is the root of power, after all. You have to learn to love the small things in life, like a hot bath. You have to love the small things, when you have nothing else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Quotes from Nevernight Trilogy by Jay Kristoff</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-nevernight-trilogy-by-jay-kristoff/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 23:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-nevernight-trilogy-by-jay-kristoff/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s not mess around here. This series has just more than quotes to offer so I have included rich descriptive texts that boil the blood and wake something deep inside. Here&amp;rsquo;s to the good times fellas. Read on for some savage blood-curdling brutalism.
The deed is done. The war is won. And at the last, gentlefriend, her song is sung. I suppose you can say you know her now, at least as well as I did.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Quotes from Realm of the Elderlings by Robin Hobb</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-realm-of-the-elderlings-by-robin-hobb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 23:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-realm-of-the-elderlings-by-robin-hobb/</guid>
      <description>Currently, I have only managed to finish off the first trilogy in the mammoth that Realm of the Elderlings happens to be but I plan to power through the series soon and add the remainder of the quotes so sit back and enjoy what I have to offer. If you feel a few hidden gems are missing, email me!
Farseer Trilogy Assassin’s Apprentice When you cut pieces out of the truth to avoid looking like a fool you end up looking like a moron instead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Quotes from Sandman (Graphic Novel) by Neil Gaiman</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-sandman-graphic-novel-by-neil-gaiman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 23:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-sandman-graphic-novel-by-neil-gaiman/</guid>
      <description>Vol 1: Preludes and Nocturnes But where shall wisdom be found? And where is the place of understanding? Man knoweth not the price thereof; neither is it found in the land of the living … for the price of wisdom is above rubies. CHORONZON: I am a dire wolf, prey-stalking, lethal prowler. MORPHEUS: I am a hunter, horse-mounted, wolf-stabbing. CHORONZON: I am a horsefly, horse-stinging, hunter-throwing. MORPHEUS: I am a spider, fly-consuming, eight legged.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Quotes from The Witcher Series by Andrzej Sapkowski</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-witcher-series-by-andrzej-sapkowski/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 23:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-witcher-series-by-andrzej-sapkowski/</guid>
      <description>The Last Wish You make as good a fisherman as a goat’s arse makes a trumpet. &amp;ldquo;Kings,” continued Calanthe, “divide people into two categories—those they order around, and those they buy—because they adhere to the old and banal truth that everyone can be bought. &amp;ldquo;The sun shines differently, the air is different, water is not as it used to be. The things we used to eat, made use of, are dying, diminishing, deteriorating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Quotes from Watchmen (Graphic Novel) by Alan Moore</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-watchmen-graphic-novel-by-alan-moore/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 23:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-watchmen-graphic-novel-by-alan-moore/</guid>
      <description>Heard joke once: Man goes to doctor. Says he&amp;rsquo;s depressed. Says life seems harsh and cruel. Says he feels all alone in a threatening world where what lies ahead is vague and uncertain. Doctor says, &amp;ldquo;Treatment is simple. Great clown Pagliacci is in town tonight. Go and see him. That should pick you up.&amp;rdquo; Man bursts into tears. Says, &amp;ldquo;But doctor&amp;hellip;I am Pagliacci. Looked at sky through smoke heavy with human fat and God was not there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Quotes from Book of the Ancestors Trilogy by Mark Lawrence</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-book-of-the-ancestors-trilogy-by-mark-lawrence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 23:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-book-of-the-ancestors-trilogy-by-mark-lawrence/</guid>
      <description>A book is as dangerous as any journey you might take. The person who closes the back cover may not be the same one that opened the front one. Treat them with respect. Your death has not been waiting for your arrival at the appointed hour: it has, for all the years of your life, been racing towards you with the fierce velocity of time&amp;rsquo;s arrow. It cannot be evaded, it cannot be bargained with, deflected or placated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Quotes from Broken Empire Trilogy by Mark Lawrence</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-broken-empire-trilogy-by-mark-lawrence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 23:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-broken-empire-trilogy-by-mark-lawrence/</guid>
      <description>Prince of Thorns Memories are dangerous things. You turn them over and over, until you know every touch and corner, but still you&amp;rsquo;ll find an edge to cut you. Each day the memories weigh a little heavier. Each day they drag you down that bit further. You wind them around you, a single thread at a time, and you weave your own shroud, you build a cocoon, and in it madness grows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DSA in Python - Dynamic Programming</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/dsapython/dp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 13:11:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/dsapython/dp/</guid>
      <description>Coin ChangeProblem Knapsack Problem Binomial CoefficientProblem Permutation CoefficientProblem Program for nth Catalan Number Matrix Chain Multiplication Edit Distance Subset Sum Problem Friends Pairing Problem Gold Mine Problem Assembly Line SchedulingProblem Painting the Fence Problem Rod Cutting Problem Longest Common Subsequence Longest Repeated Subsequence Longest Increasing Subsequence Space Optimized Solution of LCS (Print only length) LCS (Longest Common Subsequence) of three strings Maximum Sum Increasing Subsequence Count all subsequences having product less than K Longest subsequence such that difference between adjacent is one Maximum subsequence sum such that no three are consecutive Egg Dropping Problem Maximum Length Chain of Pairs Maximum size square sub-matrix with all 1s Maximum sum of pairs with specific difference Min Cost PathProblem Maximum difference of zeros and ones in binary string Minimum number of jumps to reach end Minimum cost to fill given weight in a bag Minimum removals from array to make max –min &amp;lt;= K Longest Common Substring Count number of ways to reacha given score in a game Count Balanced Binary Trees of Height h Smallest sum contiguous subarray Unbounded Knapsack (Repetition of items allowed) Largest Independent Set Problem Partition problem Longest Palindromic Subsequence Count All Palindromic Subsequence in a given String Longest Palindromic Substring Longest alternating subsequence Weighted Job Scheduling Coin game winner where every player has three choices Count Derangements (Permutation such that no element appears in its original position) Maximum profit by buying and selling a share at most twice Optimal Strategy for a Game Optimal Binary Search Tree Palindrome PartitioningProblem Word Wrap Problem Mobile Numeric Keypad Problem Boolean Parenthesization Problem Largest rectangular sub-matrix whose sum is 0 Maximum sum rectangle in a 2D matrix Maximum profit by buying and selling a share at most k times Find if a string is interleaved of two other strings Coin ChangeProblem &amp;#34;&amp;#34;&amp;#34; Given an unlimited supply of coins of given denominations, find the total number of distinct ways to get the desired change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DSA in Python - Elementry Algos</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/dsapython/elementry-algos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 23:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/dsapython/elementry-algos/</guid>
      <description>Check Leap Year Generate Random Number Largest No of 3 Prime Number Factorial Prime Number Intervals Fibonacci Sequence Armstrong Number Decimal to Binary/Hexadecimal/Octal GCD LCM Factorial Using Recursion 10 Triange Pattern Programs Check Leap Year year = 2000 # divided by 100 means century year (ending with 00) century year divided by 400 is leap year if (year % 400 == 0) and (year % 100 == 0): print(&amp;#34;{0} is a leap year&amp;#34;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DSA in Python - Graph</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/dsapython/graph/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 13:14:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/dsapython/graph/</guid>
      <description>Implement Graph Implement Weighted Graph Implement BFS algorithm Implement DFS Algo Detect Cycle in Directed Graph using BFS/DFS Algo Detect Cycle in UnDirected Graph using BFS/DFS Algo Minimum Step by Knight flood fill algo Clone a graph Making wired Connections word Ladder Dijkstra algo Implement Topological Sort Minimum time taken by each job to be completed given by a Directed Acyclic Graph Find whether it is possible to finish all tasks or not from given dependencies Find the no.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DSA in Python - Greedy</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/dsapython/greedy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 13:14:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/dsapython/greedy/</guid>
      <description>Activity Selection Problem Huffman Coding Water Connection Problem Fractional Knapsack Problem Greedy Algorithm to find Minimum number of Coins Maximum trains for which stoppage can be provided Minimum Platforms Problem Buy Maximum Stocks if i stocks can be bought on i-th day Find the minimum and maximum amount to buy all N candies Minimum Cost to cut a board into squares Check if it is possible to survive on Island Maximum product subset of an array Maximize array sum after K negations Maximize the sum of arr[i]*i Maximum sum of absolute difference of an array Maximize sum of consecutive differences in a circular array Minimum sum of absolute difference of pairs of two arrays Program for Shortest Job First (or SJF) CPU Scheduling Program for Least Recently Used (LRU) Page Replacement algorithm Smallest subset with sum greater than all other elements Chocolate Distribution Problem DEFKIN -Defense of a Kingdom DIEHARD -DIE HARD GERGOVIA -Wine trading in Gergovia Picking Up Chicks CHOCOLA –Chocolate ARRANGE -Arranging Amplifiers K Centers Problem Minimum Cost of ropes Find smallest number with given number of digits and sum of digits Rearrange characters in a string such that no two adjacent are same Find maximum sum possible equal sum of three stacks Activity Selection Problem &amp;#34;&amp;#34;&amp;#34; There is one meeting room in a firm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DSA in Python - Heap</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/dsapython/heap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 13:14:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/dsapython/heap/</guid>
      <description>Implement a Maxheap/MinHeap using arrays and recursion. (Heapify) Sort an Array using heap. (HeapSort) Maximum of all subarrays of size k. “k” largest element in an array Kth smallest and largest element in an unsorted array Merge “K” sorted arrays. Merge 2 Binary Max Heaps Kth largest sum continuous subarrays Merge “K” Sorted Linked Lists Smallest range in “K” Lists Median in a stream of Integers Check if a Binary Tree is Heap Convert BST to Min Heap Convert min heap to max heap Minimum sum of two numbers formed from digits of an array Implement a Maxheap/MinHeap using arrays and recursion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DSA in Python - Linked List</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/dsapython/ll/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 13:14:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/dsapython/ll/</guid>
      <description>Write a Program to reverse the Linked List. (Both Iterative and recursive) Reverse a Linked List in group of Given Size. Write a program to Detect and Delete loop in a linked list. Find the starting point of the loop. Remove Duplicates in a sorted Linked List. Remove Duplicates in a Un-sorted Linked List. Write a Program to Move the last element to Front in a Linked List. Add “1” to a number represented as a Linked List.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DSA in Python - Matrix</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/dsapython/matrix/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 13:14:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/dsapython/matrix/</guid>
      <description>Spiral traversal on a Matrix Search an element in a matrix Find median in a row wise sorted matrix Find row with maximum no. of 1&amp;rsquo;s Print elements in sorted order using row-column wise sorted matrix Maximum size rectangle Find a specific pair in matrix Rotate matrix by 90 degrees Kth smallest element in a row-column wise sorted matrix Common elements in all rows of a given matrix Spiral traversal on a Matrix def spiralOrder(matrix): ans = [] if (len(matrix) == 0): return ans m = len(matrix) n = len(matrix[0]) seen = [[0 for _ in range(n)] for _ in range(m)] dr = [0, 1, 0, -1] dc = [1, 0, -1, 0] x = 0 y = 0 di = 0 # Iterate from 0 to R * C - 1 for _ in range(m * n): ans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DSA in Python - Search and Sort</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/dsapython/search-and-sort/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 13:14:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/dsapython/search-and-sort/</guid>
      <description>Bubble Sort Selection Sort Insertion Sort Merge Sort Quick Sort Counting Sort Heap Sort Radix Sort Linear Search Binary Search Interpolation Search Find first and last positions of an element in a sorted array Find a Fixed Point (Value equal to index) in a given array Search in a rotated sorted array square root of an integer Find the repeating and the missing Searching in an array where adjacent differ by at most k find a pair with a given difference find two elements that sum to a given value - TwoSum find four elements that sum to a given value - ThreeSum find four elements that sum to a given value - FourSum maximum sum such that no 2 elements are adjacent Count triplet with sum smaller than a given value print all subarrays with 0 sum Product array Puzzle Sort array according to count of set bits minimum no.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DSA in Python - Stacks and Queues</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/dsapython/stack-and-queue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 13:14:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/dsapython/stack-and-queue/</guid>
      <description>Implement Stack from Scratch Implement Queue from Scratch Implement 2 stack in an array find the middle element of a stack Implement &amp;ldquo;N&amp;rdquo; stacks in an Array Check the expression has valid or Balanced parenthesis or not. Reverse a String using Stack Design a Stack that supports getMin() in O(1) time and O(1) extra space. Find the next Greater element The celebrity Problem Evaluation of Postfix expression Reverse a stack using recursion Sort a Stack using recursion Merge Overlapping Intervals Largest rectangular Area in Histogram Length of the Longest Valid Substring Expression contains redundant bracket or not Implement Stack using Queue Implement Stack using Deque Stack Permutations (Check if an array is stack permutation of other) Implement Queue using Stack Implement &amp;ldquo;n&amp;rdquo; queue in an array Implement a Circular queue LRU Cache Implementation Reverse a Queue using recursion Reverse the first “K” elements of a queue Interleave the first half of the queue with second half Find the first circular tour that visits all Petrol Pumps Minimum time required to rot all oranges Distance of nearest cell having 1 in a binary matrix First negative integer in every window of size “k” Check if all levels of two trees are anagrams or not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DSA in Python - Strings</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/dsapython/string/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 13:14:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/dsapython/string/</guid>
      <description>Check whether a String is Palindrome or not Find Duplicate characters in a string Write a Code to check whether one string is a rotation of another Write a Program to check whether a string is a valid shuffle of two strings or not Count and Say problem Write a program to find the longest Palindrome in a string.[ Longest palindromic Substring] Find Longest Recurring Subsequence in String Print all Subsequences of a string.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DSA in Python - Binary Search Trees</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/dsapython/binary-search-tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 13:10:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/dsapython/binary-search-tree/</guid>
      <description>Find a value in a BST Deletion of a node in a BST Find min and max value in a BST Find inorder successor and inorder predecessor in a BST Check if a tree is a BST or not Populate Inorder successor of all nodes Find LCA of 2 nodes in a BST Construct BST from preorder traversal Convert Binary tree into BST Convert a normal BST into a Balanced BST Merge two BST Find Kth largest element and Kth smallest element in a BST Count pairs from 2 BST whose sum is equal to given value &amp;ldquo;X&amp;rdquo; Find the median of BST in O(n) time and O(1) space Count BST nodes that lie in a given range Replace every element with the least greater element on its right Given &amp;ldquo;n&amp;rdquo; appointments, find the conflicting appointments Preorder to Postorder Check whether BST contains Dead end Largest BST in a Binary Tree Flatten BST to sorted list Find a value in a BST class Node: def __init__(self, data, left=None, right=None): self.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DSA in Python - Binary Trees</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/dsapython/binary-tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 13:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/dsapython/binary-tree/</guid>
      <description>Level order traversal AKA BFS Reverse Level Order traversal Height of a tree Diameter of a tree Mirror of a tree / Invert Binary Tree Inorder, Preorder and Postorder Tree Traversal (Recursive Method) Left View of a tree Right View of Tree Top View of a tree Bottom View of a tree Zig-Zag traversal of a binary tree Check if a tree is balanced or not Diagonal Traversal of a Binary tree Boundary traversal of a Binary tree Construct Binary Tree from String with Bracket Representation Convert Binary tree into Doubly Linked List Convert Binary tree into Sum tree Construct Binary tree from Inorder and preorder traversal Find minimum swaps required to convert a Binary tree into BST Check if Binary tree is Sum tree or not Check if all leaf nodes are at same level or not Check if a Binary Tree contains duplicate subtrees of size 2 or more Check if 2 trees are mirror or not Sum of Nodes on the Longest path from root to leaf node Check if given graph is tree or not Find Largest subtree sum in a tree Maximum Sum of nodes in Binary tree such that no two are adjacent Print all &amp;ldquo;K&amp;rdquo; Sum paths in a Binary tree Find Least Common Ancestor in a Binary tree Find distance between 2 nodes in a Binary tree Kth Ancestor of node in a Binary tree Find all Duplicate subtrees in a Binary tree Tree Isomorphism Problem Level order traversal AKA BFS class Node: def __init__(self, key): self.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DSA in Python - Trie</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/dsapython/trie/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 13:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/dsapython/trie/</guid>
      <description>Construct a trie from scratch Find shortest unique prefix for every word in a given list Word Break Problem | (Trie solution) Given a sequence of words, print all anagrams together Print unique rows in a given boolean matrix Construct a trie from scratch class TrieNode: def __init__(self): self.children = [None]*26 # isEndOfWord is True if node represent the end of the word self.isEndOfWord = False class Trie: def __init__(self): self.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DSA in Python - Arrays</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/dsapython/arrays/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 23:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/dsapython/arrays/</guid>
      <description>Reverse the array Find the maximum and minimum element in an array Find the &amp;ldquo;Kth&amp;rdquo; max and min element of an array Given an array which consists of only 0, 1 and 2. Sort the array without using any sorting algo Move all the negative elements to one side of the array Find the Union and Intersection of the two sorted arrays Write a program to cyclically rotate an array by one Find Largest sum contiguous Subarray [V.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DSA in Python - Backtracking</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/dsapython/backtracking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 23:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/dsapython/backtracking/</guid>
      <description>Rat in a maze Problem Printing all solutions in N-Queen Problem Word Break Problem using Backtracking Remove Invalid Parentheses Sudoku Solver m-Colouring Problem Print all palindromic partitions of a string Subset Sum Problem The Knight’s tour problem Tug of War Find shortest safe route in a path with landmines Combinational Sum Find Maximum number possible by doing at-most K swaps Print all permutations of a string Find if there is a path of more than k length from a source Longest Possible Route in a Matrix with Hurdles Print all possible paths from top left to bottom right of a mXn matrix Partition of a set intoK subsets with equal sum Find the K-th Permutation Sequence of first N natural numbers Rat in a maze Problem &amp;#34;&amp;#34;&amp;#34; N = 4 m[][] = {{1, 0, 0, 0}, {1, 1, 0, 1}, {1, 1, 0, 0}, {0, 1, 1, 1}} Output: DDRDRR DRDDRR Explanation: The rat can reach the destination at (3, 3) from (0, 0) by two paths - DRDDRR and DDRDRR, when printed in sorted order we get DDRDRR DRDDRR.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
