<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Book Quotes on Atharva Shah</title>
    <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/tags/book-quotes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Book Quotes on Atharva Shah</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 23:18:34 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://atharvashah.netlify.app/tags/book-quotes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Best Quotes from H.P. Lovecraft</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-h.p.-lovecraft/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 23:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-h.p.-lovecraft/</guid>
      <description>A chieftain of the macabre and the weird, H.P. Lovecraft is one of the most influential horror writers of the 20th century. His stories are filled with the supernatural and the occult and his works have inspired many other writers, including Stephen King, Neil Gaiman, and Clive Barker. Here are some of the best quotes from H.P. Lovecraft. My very personal favorites.
There are not many persons who know what wonders are opened to them in the stories and visions of their youth; for when as children we learn and dream, we think but half-formed thoughts, and when as men we try to remember, we are dulled and prosaic with the poison of life</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Quotes from First Law Trilogy by Joe Abercrombie</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-first-law-trilogy-by-joe-abercrombie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 23:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-first-law-trilogy-by-joe-abercrombie/</guid>
      <description>The Blade Itself Once you&amp;rsquo;ve got a task to do, it&amp;rsquo;s better to do it than live with the fear of it. The more you learn, the more you realize how little you know. Still, the struggle itself is worthwhile. Knowledge is the root of power, after all. You have to learn to love the small things in life, like a hot bath. You have to love the small things, when you have nothing else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Quotes from Nevernight Trilogy by Jay Kristoff</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-nevernight-trilogy-by-jay-kristoff/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 23:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-nevernight-trilogy-by-jay-kristoff/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s not mess around here. This series has just more than quotes to offer so I have included rich descriptive texts that boil the blood and wake something deep inside. Here&amp;rsquo;s to the good times fellas. Read on for some savage blood-curdling brutalism.
The deed is done. The war is won. And at the last, gentlefriend, her song is sung. I suppose you can say you know her now, at least as well as I did.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Quotes from Realm of the Elderlings by Robin Hobb</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-realm-of-the-elderlings-by-robin-hobb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 23:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-realm-of-the-elderlings-by-robin-hobb/</guid>
      <description>Currently, I have only managed to finish off the first trilogy in the mammoth that Realm of the Elderlings happens to be but I plan to power through the series soon and add the remainder of the quotes so sit back and enjoy what I have to offer. If you feel a few hidden gems are missing, email me!
Farseer Trilogy Assassin’s Apprentice When you cut pieces out of the truth to avoid looking like a fool you end up looking like a moron instead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Quotes from Sandman (Graphic Novel) by Neil Gaiman</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-sandman-graphic-novel-by-neil-gaiman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 23:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-sandman-graphic-novel-by-neil-gaiman/</guid>
      <description>Vol 1: Preludes and Nocturnes But where shall wisdom be found? And where is the place of understanding? Man knoweth not the price thereof; neither is it found in the land of the living … for the price of wisdom is above rubies. CHORONZON: I am a dire wolf, prey-stalking, lethal prowler. MORPHEUS: I am a hunter, horse-mounted, wolf-stabbing. CHORONZON: I am a horsefly, horse-stinging, hunter-throwing. MORPHEUS: I am a spider, fly-consuming, eight legged.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Quotes from The Witcher Series by Andrzej Sapkowski</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-witcher-series-by-andrzej-sapkowski/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 23:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-witcher-series-by-andrzej-sapkowski/</guid>
      <description>The Last Wish You make as good a fisherman as a goat’s arse makes a trumpet. &amp;ldquo;Kings,” continued Calanthe, “divide people into two categories—those they order around, and those they buy—because they adhere to the old and banal truth that everyone can be bought. &amp;ldquo;The sun shines differently, the air is different, water is not as it used to be. The things we used to eat, made use of, are dying, diminishing, deteriorating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Quotes from Watchmen (Graphic Novel) by Alan Moore</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-watchmen-graphic-novel-by-alan-moore/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 23:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-watchmen-graphic-novel-by-alan-moore/</guid>
      <description>Heard joke once: Man goes to doctor. Says he&amp;rsquo;s depressed. Says life seems harsh and cruel. Says he feels all alone in a threatening world where what lies ahead is vague and uncertain. Doctor says, &amp;ldquo;Treatment is simple. Great clown Pagliacci is in town tonight. Go and see him. That should pick you up.&amp;rdquo; Man bursts into tears. Says, &amp;ldquo;But doctor&amp;hellip;I am Pagliacci. Looked at sky through smoke heavy with human fat and God was not there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Quotes from Book of the Ancestors Trilogy by Mark Lawrence</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-book-of-the-ancestors-trilogy-by-mark-lawrence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 23:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-book-of-the-ancestors-trilogy-by-mark-lawrence/</guid>
      <description>A book is as dangerous as any journey you might take. The person who closes the back cover may not be the same one that opened the front one. Treat them with respect. Your death has not been waiting for your arrival at the appointed hour: it has, for all the years of your life, been racing towards you with the fierce velocity of time&amp;rsquo;s arrow. It cannot be evaded, it cannot be bargained with, deflected or placated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Quotes from Broken Empire Trilogy by Mark Lawrence</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-broken-empire-trilogy-by-mark-lawrence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 23:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/blog/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-broken-empire-trilogy-by-mark-lawrence/</guid>
      <description>Prince of Thorns Memories are dangerous things. You turn them over and over, until you know every touch and corner, but still you&amp;rsquo;ll find an edge to cut you. Each day the memories weigh a little heavier. Each day they drag you down that bit further. You wind them around you, a single thread at a time, and you weave your own shroud, you build a cocoon, and in it madness grows.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
