<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>💻 Tech Posts on Atharva Shah</title>
    <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 💻 Tech Posts on Atharva Shah</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 01:18:34 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sales Data Analysis with Python</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/sales-data-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 01:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/sales-data-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Introduction ABC Private Limited, a retail company, aims to gain valuable insights into their customers&amp;rsquo; purchasing habits. By analyzing the provided summary of high-volume product purchase history, which includes customer demographics and product details, ABC can uncover patterns and trends in customer spending across different product categories.
We will explore the analysis step-by-step using the test.csv and train.csv files. Through a combination of theoretical explanations and practical demonstrations, we will delve into data preprocessing, exploratory data analysis, feature engineering, and model building.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Product Series Launch!</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/gumroad-dsa-announcement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 01:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/gumroad-dsa-announcement/</guid>
      <description>Boost Your Interview Success with our Exclusive Digital Product Series We are thrilled to announce the launch of our brand new series of digital products on Gumroad, designed to help you excel in your interviews and land your dream job! Our products are carefully crafted to provide you with the necessary tools and resources to master key concepts, enhance your problem-solving skills, and confidently tackle coding interviews.
Introducing the First Set of Resources We are excited to release the first few resources that are now available for purchase at an incredibly affordable rate:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting Up CI/CD to Netlify for Static Sites via Github</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/netlify-ci-cd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 19:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/netlify-ci-cd/</guid>
      <description>Description I. Introduction II. Setting Up a Netlify Account III. Setting Up CI/CD to Netlify Configuring the Build Settings on Netlify Configuring the Deployment Settings on Netlify IV. Setting Up CI/CD with Github Actions Introduction to Github Actions Creating a Github Actions Workflow for the Static Site Configuring the Workflow to Deploy to Netlify V. Best Practices for CI/CD with Netlify and Github VI. Troubleshooting CI/CD Issues VII. Conclusion Description This article provides step-by-step instructions on how to set up continuous integration and continuous deployment (CI/CD) to Netlify for static site deployments using Github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Django Crypto App Part 3: Wrap-Up and Testing</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/django-crypto-app/part3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 23:20:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/django-crypto-app/part3/</guid>
      <description>Here, we will be defining the functional requirements and give you the overview of what we are building, the approach, the high-level design and the project setup using Django.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Django Crypto App Part 2: Templates, Views and URLs</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/django-crypto-app/part2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 23:19:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/django-crypto-app/part2/</guid>
      <description>Here, we will be defining the functional requirements and give you the overview of what we are building, the approach, the high-level design and the project setup using Django.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Django Crypto App Part 1: Functional Requirements and Setup</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/django-crypto-app/part1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 23:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/django-crypto-app/part1/</guid>
      <description>Here, we will be defining the functional requirements and give you the overview of what we are building, the approach, the high-level design and the project setup using Django.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Django ORM Cheatsheet &#43; Exercises</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/django-orm-exercises/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 01:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/django-orm-exercises/</guid>
      <description>Querying Django Models with Examples Terminology Models Used in the Examples QuerySet API Exercises Query 1: Fetching all books from the database Query 2: Fetching selected columns from the Books table Query 3: Filtering records based on a condition Query 4: Filtering records based on multiple conditions Query 5: Searching records based on a substring Query 6: Retrieve authors with specific primary keys Query 7: Retrieve authors who joined after a specific date Query 8: Retrieve distinct publisher last name Query 9: Retrieve the latest joined author and the earliest joined publisher Query 10: Retrieve the first name, last name, and join date of the most recently joined author Query 11: Retrieve Authors Joined After 2013 Query 12: Calculate Total Price of Books Written by Popular Authors Query 13: Retrieve Titles of Books Written by Authors with &amp;lsquo;a&amp;rsquo; in their Firstname Query 14: Calculate Average Book Price of Selected Authors Query 15: Retrieve first name of authors and their recommended author&amp;rsquo;s first name Query 16: Retrieve authors whose books are published by a specific publisher Query 17: Add followers to an author Query 18: Set followers for an author Query 19: Add a follower to an author Query 20: Remove a follower from an author Query 21: Retrieve the first names of all authors followed by the user with primary key (pk) equal to 1 Query 22: Retrieve all authors who have books with titles containing the string &amp;ldquo;tle&amp;rdquo; Query 23: Retrieve all authors whose first name starts with the letter &amp;ldquo;a&amp;rdquo; and either have a popularity score greater than 5 or joined the platform after the year 2014 Query 24: Retrieve the author with primary key (pk) equal to 1 Query 25: Retrieve the first 10 authors in the database Query 26: Retrieve the first and last author in the database with a popularity score of 7 Query 27: Retrieve all authors whose joindate year is greater than or equal to 2012, popularity_score is greater than or equal to 4, joindate day is greater than or equal to 12, and firstname starts with &amp;lsquo;a&amp;rsquo; Query 28: Retrieve all authors whose joindate year is not equal to 2012 Query 29: Retrieve the oldest joindate among all authors, the newest joindate among all authors, the average popularity_score of all authors, and the sum of price of all books Query 30: Retrieve all authors who have not been recommended by anyone Query 31: Retrieve all books that have an author, and all books that have an author who has not been recommended by anyone Query 32: Calculate the sum of the price of all books authored by the author with primary key (pk) equal to 1 Query 33: Retrieve the title of the most recently published book Query 34: Calculate the average price of all books Query 35: Calculate the maximum popularity score of all the publishers that have published a book written by the author with primary key 1 Query 36: Count Authors with Books containing &amp;lsquo;ab&amp;rsquo; in the title Query 37: Filter Authors by Number of Followers Query 38: Average Popularity Score of Authors who joined after 20th Sep 2014 Query 39: Filter Books by Authors who have written more than 10 Books Query 40: Filter Books by Title Count Conclusion Querying Django Models with Examples In Django, querying the database is an essential task when working with models.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use ChatGPT to Generate Project UML Diagrams: A Step-by-Step Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/uml-diagrams-with-chatgpt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 01:19:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/uml-diagrams-with-chatgpt/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you tired of spending hours designing UML diagrams for your projects? Look no further than ChatGPT, a powerful language model that can generate PlantUML code based on your project description. In this tutorial, we will guide you through the steps to use ChatGPT to generate UML diagrams for your projects in just a few clicks.
Step 1: Write Your Project Description The first step is to write your project description or title.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I am Learning in 2023</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/what-i-am-learning-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 01:19:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/what-i-am-learning-2023/</guid>
      <description>Django 🚀2023 is here, and I&amp;rsquo;m ready to blast off into the world of new tech! First up on my list is the one and only Django 🤘. This bad boy is known for its ease of use and flexibility, plus it&amp;rsquo;s got a huge community of cool kids using it. I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to dive deeper and discover all its hidden gems like the ORM, admin interface, and built-in security features.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating into the Future: An Exploration of Effective Accelerationism and its Impact on AI and Society</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/effective-accelerationism/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 01:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/effective-accelerationism/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Brief overview of accelerationism The advent of AI and its impact on society Theories of Accelerationism Historical context of accelerationism Left and right-wing accelerationism Critiques of accelerationism AI and the Future of Society Advancements in AI technology Potential consequences of widespread AI integration Ethical considerations of AI development Accelerationism and Transhumanism: A Complex Intersection The intersection of accelerationism and transhumanism Potential benefits and drawbacks of merging technology with humanity Final thoughts on the Post-AI Society Introduction Yo, what&amp;rsquo;s good, internet?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating victory at CRIF Hackathon 2023</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/crif-hackathon-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 23:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/posts/tech/crif-hackathon-2023/</guid>
      <description>Winning a hackathon is an incredible feeling, and it&amp;rsquo;s even more special when it&amp;rsquo;s your very first one. The adrenaline rush of competing against some of the brightest minds in the industry, the satisfaction of solving complex problems, and the thrill of being recognized for your hard work are all emotions that are hard to put into words. In this article, I&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through the journey of our team who recently won their first ever hackathon, the CRIF Hackathon 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
