<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Mike Ma on Atharva Shah</title>
    <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/tags/mike-ma/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mike Ma on Atharva Shah</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 02:18:34 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://atharvashah.netlify.app/tags/mike-ma/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Best Quotes from Gothic Violence by Mika Ma</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/personal/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-gothic-violence-by-mike-ma/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 02:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/personal/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-gothic-violence-by-mike-ma/</guid>
      <description>Emerging from the literary depths, following the consuming voyage through &amp;ldquo;Harassment Architecture,&amp;rdquo; I eagerly embarked upon the haunting terrain of &amp;ldquo;Gothic Violence.&amp;rdquo; In this eagerly awaited sequel, my anticipation was richly rewarded, for within its pages lie potent and evocative fragments of prose that reverberate with profound resonance. While the quantity may be lesser than its predecessor, the impact remains undiminished, as the narrative unfurls with a potent force, relentlessly piercing the reader&amp;rsquo;s consciousness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Quotes from Harassment Architechture by Mika Ma</title>
      <link>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/personal/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-harassment-architechture-by-mike-ma/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 01:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atharvashah.netlify.app/personal/book-quotes/the-best-quotes-from-harassment-architechture-by-mike-ma/</guid>
      <description>Immersed within the profound literary labyrinth that is Mike Ma&amp;rsquo;s oeuvre, I stumbled upon an enigmatic tapestry of words that left me astounded, pondering why this luminary artist had not yet ascended to the pinnacles of recognition. Within the tapestry of his creations, one finds a captivating amalgamation of satire, philosophy, and humor that defies conventional categorization. Yet, it is not through the predictable lens of conventional narratives that Ma&amp;rsquo;s genius shines.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
